[Music]
means quarantine or social isolation first since we do not have
vaccine or specific treatment at this time the only effective way to
to avoid contagion is to keep it at our home as much as possible
possible time because the truth is how you may have already read and how
also the funds we are teaching the symptoms can be very
mild and you are already infected, therefore it is very difficult for us to differentiate
if we have an infection therefore the call is to stay at home and
also try to reduce the intimate contact that one has with their relatives
especially if they already have respiratory symptoms
if a person in the house has respiratory symptoms all pain
muscle, headache, etc. Ideally, you should maintain isolation in
their house as much as possible this especially can be concluded when they are adults
self-employed stay in their rooms occupy the same eating utensils
separated from other people in the house as well as in the
hygiene measures the important thing is to maintain this isolation at least
while they have respiratory symptoms if you are already
diagnosed with this kobin infection then isolation has to be
even more rigorous and complete it for at least 14 days which is the time where
we are excreting this virus this is an infection that has us
health systems are concerned, we are all alert and what
We ask that you please follow the instructions of the authority consult
when they have doubts to the corresponding health services because we need
protect them all [Music]