Hello, I am Blanca and I am 6 years old and it is in my question, how is the coronavirus spread
HEADBOARD
How do we get the coronavirus? When you sneeze, cough and even talk,
Thousands of tiny droplets of saliva are expelled from your mouth. They're so
small ones that can remain floating in the air for several minutes, and if
sneeze or cough loudly, they shoot out with such force that they
reach several meters away staining surfaces and objects at their
He passed. It is completely normal. The problem comes if you are sick. Yes
you have a cold or flu or coronavirus, in addition to saliva those micro
droplets contain viral particles. If at that moment some person
is nearby, you can breathe in those droplets with viruses and become infected. If you touch a
stained surface and then inadvertently touching your face, the virus can also
enter through your mouth, nose or eyes. This is how you can get infected with the virus. But,
What happens when it enters the body? Once inside the coronavirus joins some
special proteins on the surface of your cells. In this way they manage to enter
and take advantage of the machinery of the cell to create thousands upon thousands of
copies of himself. The new viruses in turn can enter other cells and
produce even more viruses. Soon there are so many viruses that the body looks for a way to
get rid of them: cough, sneeze ... and with it, thousands of droplets with viruses
they shoot out. Does it sound familiar to you? We have returned to the beginning.
This is how these viruses manage to survive and pass from one person to another.
But what can we do to stop it? What steps can we take to not
infect us or pass it on to other people?
Surely seeing how viruses are transmitted you have already thought of several
ways to avoid it, but we are going to summarize them all so that we do not
none in the pipeline. 1. wash your hands with soap and water often to
thus eliminate possible viruses and microbes 2 when you sneeze or cough, never, never
do it directly on a person. Use a handkerchief or elbow if you don't have
one by hand. It is better not to use your hands. When we use our hands we are
filling with viruses and then we can spread these viruses by touching something.
3. Keep a safe distance of at least 2 meters from people. So you avoid
that when you speak, breathe or cough, possible viruses reach your body. 4. Use
mask when you are going to be around other people. Thus, those microdroplets
with viruses are trapped inside and cannot get out, and in turn the droplets that
there are in the air they cannot enter your body. It is the best possible barrier.
5. And finally, if you are sick, stay home. This way you avoid passing the virus to others
people and you can rest and heal calmly. As you can see, they are very
simple, but thanks to them we prevent viruses from spreading uncontrollably and
that vulnerable people can fall seriously ill. Meanwhile, the
Scientists around the world are going crazy creating a special vaccine against
the coronavirus. When we have it, with a simple injection we will all be
protected against the virus. There is less left to achieve it. If you liked it
what you have seen, like it, share it, and subscribe to the channel, and
remember, you too are science